{
    "id": "947724cdd4e74d8396a1a9e43421b13f",
    "title": "Parts Of Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She had to move out of that tough ...................................",
            "description": "We need a noun here.",
            "answers": [
                "neighborly",
                "neighboring",
                "neighborhood"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The townsfolk were quite ........................................... when we moved here.",
            "description": "Neighborly means friendly. ",
            "answers": [
                "neighbor",
                "neighboring",
                "neighborly"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is so ...................................... she jumps at the slightest noise.",
            "description": "We use a noun or adjective as the complement of a verb of incomplete predication. ",
            "answers": [
                "nervous",
                "nervously",
                "nervousness"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is charming ............................................. I don't quite trust him.",
            "description": "Nevertheless is a transitional adverb. It is similar to however.",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "despite",
                "nevertheless"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She gave me a ............................................ answer.",
            "description": "Noncommittal can mean indefinite or reserved. ",
            "answers": [
                "nonchalant",
                "noncommittal",
                "nominal"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There will be a ................................................ charge for the lunch.",
            "description": "Nominal can mean low or small. ",
            "answers": [
                "nominate",
                "nominal",
                "nominee"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Paying taxes is ............................................",
            "description": "Obligatory means compulsory or mandatory. ",
            "answers": [
                "obligation",
                "obligational",
                "obligatory"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It is hard to be polite to ........................................... people.",
            "description": "Obtrusive means intrusive or interfering. ",
            "answers": [
                "obtrusive",
                "obstructive",
                "obstrusive"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The weather was good except for an .............................................. shower.",
            "description": "Occasional is the adjective form. ",
            "answers": [
                "occasion",
                "occasional",
                "occasionally"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The youth's language was .........................................",
            "description": "Offensive means insulting. ",
            "answers": [
                "offense",
                "offensive",
                "offend"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Inflation will ........................................... the pay raise.",
            "description": "Offset can mean nullify. ",
            "answers": [
                "offset",
                "off set",
                "ofset"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "How ......................................... do you visit your parents?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "often",
                "ever",
                "sometimes"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}